Morning's here
美…好…的…
The morning's here
早晨又来到
Sunshine is here
阳光露脸
The sky is clear
晴空万里
The morning's here
美好的早晨又来到
Hey!
Do you have to do that? It's Saturday!
你一定要唱吗？今天是星期六
Oh,come on!
别这样嘛
Morning's here!
早晨来到了
I hate this apartment!
我恨这层公寓
I hate this wall color! I hate that it still smells like bird!
我恨墙壁的颜色 我恨这里还是有鸡鸭的味道
I hate that singing guy!
我恨那个唱歌的人
Are you kidding? I love that guy!
不会吧，我好喜欢他
Morning's here
美好的早晨又来到…
Stop it!
闭嘴
I will kill you.
小心我宰了你
I hate that my room is so small.
我恨我的房间那么小
I have all the space I need. Do what I did.
我就觉得空间够用，学学我吧
You don't even have a bed. You sleep in a ball on the floor!
你连床都没有 睡在地上的懒骨头
I am tired of your bellyaching.
你别再碎碎念了
I've worked hard to make this a nice place for us.
我很努力的把这里布置舒适
I know. I'm so sorry.
我知道，对不起
I'm sorry,okay?
没关系
It's a great apartment!
看吧，这里很好
Shut up! This place is a hole!
闭嘴，这里烂死了
The One with All the Haste
本集播出：“闪电决定”
rainystar压制iPod-MP4
I still can't believe you've got an earring!
我还是不敢相信你穿了耳洞
I know,I know. Who am l? David Bowie?
我知道 我是谁？大卫鲍伊？
He does that?
他会那样吗？
I don't know. Whatever.
不晓得，随便
I think it makes you look really dangerous.
你这样看起来好危险
Oh,I know.
我知道
You know what?
你知道吗？
I never would've gotten this if it weren't for you.
要不是你，我永远不会穿耳洞
When I'm with you,I'm like...
真的，跟你在一起时
...this whole other guy. I love that guy!
我就变了一个人 我爱那个人
I mean,I love you too. A lot.
我也很爱你
But that guy!
不过那个人…
I love that guy!
我爱那个人
I love both of you.
我爱你们两个
I wish I didn't have to go.
我好不想走
Then don't.
那就别走
Stay here. Don't go so soon to London.
留下来 别急着回伦敦
Just one more day.
再留1天就好
Please don't do this to me again.
罗斯，别再引诱我了
I'd stay,but I've already missed so much work. They'll fire me.
我也想 但我请了那么多假，会被开除
So? Then you could stay as long as you want.
那你就可以尽情留下来了
I wish I could.
我也很想
Oh,no. Don't start packing.
不要，不要打包
Come on!
拜托啦
I don't think you understand packing.
那不叫打包
I don't want to leave it till last. Last time,I left my knickers here.
我不想拖到最后一刻 上次我把球鞋忘在这里
Yeah,I know. I tried them on.
我知道，我有偷穿
You didn't!
不会吧
No,I didn't. I didn't want to be "that guy."
骗你的，我不想学另一个我
Excuse me?
什么？
Your pants.
你的裤子
Oh yeah! You like them?
喔对，你喜欢吗？
I went to a used-clothes store and got maternity stuff.
我去二手衣店买孕妇装
These are so comfortable.
这条裤子好舒服
Pheebs,those are Santa pants.
菲比，那是圣诞裤
Santa pants.
什么？ 圣诞裤
Santa Claus' pants.
圣诞老人的裤子
No. They're maternity pants.
才不是，这是孕妇裤
They even came with a list of baby names. See?
你看，还附赠宝宝姓名表
These names are good, and these are bad.
这些名字好，这些名字不好
Hey,Phoebes.
菲比
So,how are the elves?
驯鹿都好吗？
I don't know. How are the...you know?
我不知道，那你…那个…
Your clothes aren't funny.
你的衣服不好玩
What should I wear to a Knicks game?
我该穿什么去看尼克队比赛？
A T-shirt that says, "l Don't Belong Here"?
上面印有 “我不看篮球”的衣服？
You have tickets?
你们有票？
Mom got Dad's season tickets in the divorce,so she gave them to me.
妈离婚时分到爸的季票 就送给我了
Apparently,they're good seats.
位子显然很好
Oh,my God! Those are almost on the floor!
天哪，几乎就在场边
I could slip Woody Allen my resume.
我可以把履历表塞给伍迪艾伦
Do you guys want these?
你们想要吗？
Yeah,we do!
废话
Well,you got them!
那就给你们 谢谢
Just give us our apartment back.
只要把这里还给我们
Oh,I didn't see that coming.
想不到有这一招
Are you serious?
你是说真的？
Come on. We know what these are worth.
我们知道你们哈死这些票了
Do you think we're stupid?
你们以为我们是白痴吗？
Not stupid. You're meaner than I thought.
不是白痴，是很恶劣
What do you say?
如何？
Forget it. I'm not giving up my bachelor pad for basketball seats.
想都别想，我才不会为了球票 放弃我的单身公寓
Your "bachelor pad"?
你的单身公寓？
Have you even had a girl here?
你带女生回来过吗？
No.
没有
But Joey has,and I usually talk to them in the morning.
但是乔伊有 我早上都会跟她们聊天
Yeah,you do!
没错
Come on!
拜托啦
Gunther,can I get two cups of chino,please?
阿甘，请给我两杯奇诺
Good one.
很有趣
Come on. Season tickets!
季票耶！
Season tickets! You know what that means?
季票耶！你知道那代表什么？
I'm not giving up the apartment.
别想了，我绝不让出那层公寓
When I was a kid,my dad's company gave season tickets...
小时候我爸的公司都会送季票
...to the No. 1 salesman every year. My dad never won.
给业绩第一的业务员 我爸从来没拿到过
Of course,he wasn't in sales. But still,I never forgot that!
不过他也不在业务部 但我还是一直耿耿于怀
Hey guys!
你们在啊
Oh,my God!
天哪
We don't make enough fun of you already?
我们笑你笑得还不够吗？
Oh,yeah. Emily convinced me to do it.
艾蜜莉说服我去穿的
You do know that Wham broke up?
你知道“轰”解散了吧？ （乔治麦可出身之二人团体）
I like it. Emily likes it. That's what counts.
我喜欢，艾蜜莉喜欢 这样最重要
So,how are you guys doing?
你们好吗？
Don't try and talk all normal with that thing in your ear.
别戴了耳环还装正常
Where's Emily?
艾蜜莉呢？
She's saying goodbye to her uncle.
去跟她舅舅道别
Didn't she,like,just get here?
她不是才刚来？ 就是嘛
Easy,tiger.
别激动，大哥
I just hate this so much.
我好讨厌这样
Every time I go pick her up at the airport,it's so great.
每次去机场接她，我都好开心
But I'm thinking,"I'll be right back in a couple of days,dropping her off."
但是我又会想 “过两天又要送她来机场了”
-So what'll you do? -There's nothing to do.
那你要怎么办？ 不怎么办
She lives there. I live here.
她住在那里，我住在这里
She'd have to move here.
她得搬来这里
She should move here.
她应该搬来这里
What?
什么？
-I can ask her to live with me. -Are you serious?
我可以叫她跟我住 你说真的吗？
-I mean,why not? -You've only known her six weeks!
为什么不行？ 你才认识她6星期
I've got a carton of milk in my fridge I've had a longer relationship with.
我冰箱里有盒牛奶放得还更久
Look,guys,when I'm with her, it's like....
我跟她在一起时
She brings out this great side of me.
她会激发出我好的一面
I mean,I love her,you know?
我爱她
And I love the milk!
我也爱那盒牛奶
But I won't ask some British girl to move in with me.
但我不会要一个英国女生 跟我同居
Joey,you say things now.
乔伊，该你说了
Look,Ross. He's right. Emily's great.
罗斯，他说得对，艾蜜莉很棒
She's great!
她很棒
But this is too soon. You'll only scare her.
但这样太快了，你只会吓到她
I don't want to do that.
我不想吓到她
You don't want to wreck it. Don't go too fast.
没错，别坏了好事，别太心急
No. You're right. I know,you're right.
你们说得对
I'm not going to do it.
我不会这样
-Thanks guys. -No problem.
谢了，两位
Just remember to wake us up before you go-go.
记得要走时摇它两下 （“轰”所唱的歌词）
It's too hard. Too hard!
太难了，太难了
All right. Last chance for the tickets.
两位，最后的机会
Otherwise,I give them to my new boyfriend,Joshua.
否则我就送给我的新男友 约书亚
No,thank you.
不用了
Wait,wait. Come on,come on! Let's trade.
等一下…拜托，跟她们换啦
The timing's perfect! I just clogged the toilet!
时机正好，我刚把马桶堵住
I want those seats. But we can't live in the small apartment...
我跟你一样想要球票 但住过这里就觉得...
...after living here! Ever read Flowers for Algernon?
...对面太小了 你看过 “献给阿尔吉浓的花束”吗？
Ever read Sports Illustrated?
有 你看过“运动画报”吗？
No,I didn't read yours!
我没偷看你的
We can go to the game tonight!
我们晚上就可以去看球
The only way I'll consider this is...
她们提出比季票更好的东西
...if they offer more than just season seats.
我才要考虑
-It's the Knicks! -Screw the Knicks!
是尼克队耶 去他的尼克队
I didn't mean that. I just meant that...
我不是那个意思 我是说...
...the apartment is worth so much more.
...这层公寓的价值要更大
And the Knicks rule.
尼克队万岁
Yeah,the Knicks rule!
对，尼克队万岁
So? Are you going to do it?
怎样？要不要？
No,we're not going to because it's not an even trade.
不要，因为这个交易不公平
All right,look.
好，听着
What if you could keep the apartment and the tickets?
要是你们能保住公寓 又拿到球票呢？
Done!
成交
Let me finish. I'm talking about a bet. Winner takes all.
让我说完，我是说我们来赌 赢的人通杀
We could get nothing.
我们可能输光光
Or everything.
或是通杀
I like that.
我喜欢
What do you say?
怎么样？ 不要
Just do it!
赌了啦
Oh! I'm convinced!
真有说服力啊
Come on,man! You know I'd do it for you.
拜托啦，我也会为你这么做
Because you're my best friend.
因为你是我最好的朋友
All right. But you can't use that again for a whole year.
好吧 但你1整年不准再用这招
I'm in.
我赌了
This is so exciting! What are you going to bet?
好兴奋喔，你们要赌什么？
We should let Phoebe decide...
就让菲比决定
...because she's the only one who's impartial,and she's so pretty.
因为只有她没有利害关系 而且她好美
I have a game!
我知道了
-This is great! -What's the game?
很棒喔 比什么？
It doesn't have a name. No,okay. Phoebe Ball!
没有名字 不，叫菲比球
No,it doesn't have a name.
不，没有名字
What is your favorite thing about trees?
摩妮卡 你最喜欢树的哪一点？
-They're green? -Good! Five points!
树是绿色的 很好，5分
Same question.
乔伊，同样的问题
-They're tall. -Three points!
树很高 3分
Both fine answers,but we were looking for leafy. Leafy.
都答得很好 但我们说的是阔叶植物
That's not even a game.
这根本不是比赛
Shut up. We're winning!
闭嘴，我们领先
You want to finish this? We get a deck of cards.
你们想速战速决？我们抽牌
High card wins. What do you say?
点数大的赢，如何？
-Let's do it! -Oh,I have cards!
好，就这么办 我刚好有牌
Yeah. Here.
在这里
No,these are the trick deck.
这是魔术牌
Here,yes.
这一副
Okay,you guys pick first.
好，你们先抽
-Four. -That's a low one!
4点 够少了
You look. I can't do it.
菲比，你看，我不敢看
What makes you think I can?
为什么我就敢看？
Ace!
1点
Why are you hugging?
你们在爽什么？
We won our apartment back!
我们把这里抢回来了
What? Ace is high! Jack,queen,king,ace!
什么？王牌最大 杰克皮蛋老K A
No! Ace is low! Ace,two,three,four!
不对，1点最小，1234
I don't know.
我不知道
Look it!
你们看
Come on,pick again!
再抽一次
Come on,apartment! Come on,apartment!
我要公寓，我要公寓
I know queen is high!
皮蛋点数很大
Not as high as....
但是大不过…
It worked! King!
成功了！老K
We pick again! We pick again!
再抽一次
-Why? -I don't know.
为什么？ 我不知道
Tickets,please.
球票请拿来
Courtside,baby!
场边区喔
Seriously,good game,though. Good game.
很精彩的比赛
What are they so mad about? They got the apartment back.
她们气什么气？ 公寓都还给她们了
No,they didn't.
没有啦
Packed while you were gone.
趁你不在打包好了
I left knickers under your pillow.
我留了双球鞋在枕头底下
Move in with me?
搬来跟我住
What?
什么？
Don't be scared. It sounds crazy, and people will say it's too soon...
别怕，我知道听起来很疯狂 别人会说太快了
...but just think. Think how great it would be.
但是你想想，那样多棒啊
I don't know.
我不知道
Leaving London....
要我离开伦敦…
My whole family lives there....
我的家人都在那里 我知道
-My job. -You'll get a job here.
我的工作 你可以在这里找工作
I always hear about them foreigners stealing American jobs.
我常听说美国人的工作 都被外国人抢走了
That could be you.
你也可以
Yeah,but it's my whole life.
但事关我的人生
You come to England.
你来英国
I would. I really would. But my son is here.
我不行，我很愿意 但我儿子在这里
I can't leave him. You don't think there's any way?
我离不开他 没别的办法了吗？
I don't think so.
我看是没有了
It would be different if it was way into the future...
如果是长久的打算就不同了
...and we were getting married.
例如结婚什么的
What?
什么？
Right. I shouldn't have said "married." Please don't go freaky on me.
好，我不该提结婚的 别被我吓到
I didn't mean it. I take it back.
我不是认真的 我没说，我收回
No. Don't.
不，不要收回
Why don't we?
何不就这么做？
Why don't we what?
做什么？
Get married.
结婚啊
You are mad!
你疯了
No,I'm not! It's perfect. It's better than you moving here.
我没有，这样很完美 比你搬来住更棒
It's us together forever, and that's what I want.
我们可以永远在一起 我就是要这样
-We've known each other six weeks! -I know.
我们才认识6星期 我知道，那又怎样？
So what? Who's to say? Does that mean we can't do it?
谁说不行？这样就不行吗？
Look. I was with Carol for four years before we got married...
听着，我跟卡萝结婚前 在一起4年
...and I wound up divorced from a pregnant lesbian.
最后跟一个怀孕的女同志离婚
I mean,this....
这么做…
This makes sense for us.
对我们是顺理成章
Our first date,we ended up spending the whole weekend in Vermont.
我们第一次约会 就跑去佛蒙特度周末
I mean,last night I got my ear pierced. Me!
昨晚我还去穿耳洞，我耶
This feels right.
这个感觉很对
Doesn't it?
不是吗？
My parents will be really mad.
我爸妈会气死
Are you saying,"Yes"? Is that "Yes"?
你答应了吗？那是好吗？
Yes.
对
-We're getting married! -Oh,my God!
我们要结婚了 天哪
We're getting married!
我们要结婚了，天哪
Come here,come here.
过来
Emily,will you marry me?
艾蜜莉，你愿意嫁给我吗？
愿意
It's a bit small.
有一点小
Damn! I thought that'd be romantic as hell.
真是的，我还以为会很浪漫
It was.
是很浪漫
Those were,like, the best seats ever!
真是史上最棒的位子
Should we give these to the girls? Like a peace offering?
要不要把衣服送给女生 表示和解？
That's very nice. Plus,they were free and too small.
好主意，反正不用钱又太小
Oh,God!
天哪
Hey,you want a beer?
你要喝酒吗？
I know!
我知道
Open up! Open up! Open up!
开门！开门
We'll discuss it in the morning.
明天早上再说
What the hell is going on?
这是怎么回事？
We took our apartment back!
我们把我们家抢回来了
I had nothing to do with it.
跟我无关
Okay,it was my idea. But I don't feel good about it.
好吧，是我的主意 但我并不好过
We are switching back right now.
我们现在就换回来
No,we're not. We're not leaving!
不要，我们不走
You'll have to. You both have jobs.
你们非走不可，你们都有工作
As soon as you do,we'll switch back! You can't stop us.
等你们去上班，我们就换回来 你们阻止不了的
-Right,Joe? -I don't know.
对吧，乔伊？ 我不晓得
What?
什么？
I don't want to move again,with....
我不想再搬了
This is our apartment and they stole
我不管，这是我们的公寓 她们偷了…
You stole!
你们偷了！
Our apartment! We won it fair and square. Twice!
我们的公寓 我们光明正大的赢了两次
And I am getting it back right now! I'm getting it back right now!
我现在就要要回来 我现在就要要回来
All right.
好
We figured you might respond this way,so we have a backup offer.
我们早料到会有这种反应
No more offers. You can't offer anything to us!
所以我们准备了备案 不要，你们搞不定我们的
-Let us keep the apartment and -As a thank you...
让我们留在这里 为了表示感谢
...Rachel and I will kiss for one minute.
瑞秋和我会接吻1分钟
-Totally worth it! -That was one good minute!
完全值得 好爽的1分钟
Good night.
晚安 晚安
-Men are such idiots. -I know.
男人真是白痴 就是啊
Can you believe something that stupid actually got us our apartment back?
那么白痴的事 居然让我们得逞了
If you had just done that after the last contest...
要是你们上次比完就这么做
...no one would have had to move at all.
谁都不必搬家
Let's pretend that's not true.
就装做没这回事
Scarf's done.
围巾织好了
Come on,come on!
快点 好
What's going on?
怎么了？
Ross has some big thing to tell everyone.
罗斯有大事要宣布
Emily and l,we decided...
艾蜜莉和我决定…
...to get married.
...要结婚
What?
什么？
Oh,are you pregnant too?
你也怀孕了？
No.
没有
When did How did you
什么… 怎么…
We just decided to go for it.
我们就是决定要结婚
We know it's a bit hasty...
这个决定是仓卒了些
...but it just feels so right.
但是… 感觉真的很对
I was just telling the guys
我正在告诉他们…
Yeah,I heard.
我听到了
I think it's great!
太好了
I'm so happy for you!
我真替你高兴
Well,yeah! Congratulations!
是啊，恭喜
I can't believe you're getting married!
你居然要结婚了
Monica and Rachel made out.
摩妮卡和瑞秋亲热
Morning's here
美…好…的…
The morning's here
早晨又来到
Sunshine is here
阳光露脸
The sky is clear
晴空万里
The morning's here
美好的早晨
-Hey,you're back! -Hey,get into gear
你回来了 准备就绪
Breakfast is near
早餐就快上桌
The dark of night has disappeared
夜晚的黑暗一扫而空
I'll see you tomorrow morning!
我们明天见 好